{"questions":[
			{
				"question":"How many horns did Triceratops have?",
				"choices":[
					{"choice":"Two"},
					{"choice":"Three"},
					{"choice":"Four"},
					{"choice":"Five"}],
				"correctAnswer":"three"
			},{
				"question":"The name dinosaur means ‘terrible lizard’.",
				"choices":[
					{"choice":"True"},
					{"choice":"False"}],
				"correctAnswer":"true"
			},{
				"question":"Which came first, the Jurassic or Cretaceous Period?",
				"choices":[
					{"choice":"Jurassic"},
					{"choice":"Cretaceous"},
					{"choice":"Both aren't prehistoric periods"},
					{"choice":"Only one of those is a prehistoric period"}],
				"correctAnswer":"Jurassic"
			},{
				"question":"Was Diplodocus a carnivore or herbivore?",
				"choices":[
					{"choice":"Carnivore"},
					{"choice":"Herbivore"},
					{"choice":"Omnivore"}],
				"correctAnswer":"herbivore"
			},{
				"question":"Tyrannosaurus rex was the biggest dinosaur ever.",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"True"},
				{"choice":"False"}],
				"correctAnswer":"false"
			},{
				"question":"Iguanodon was one of three dinosaurs that inspired the appearance of Godzilla.",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"True"},
				{"choice":"False"}],
				"correctAnswer":"True"
			},
			{
				"question":"Did Theropods such as Allosaurus and Carnotaurus move on two legs or four?",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"Two"},
				{"choice":"Four"}],
				"correctAnswer":"two"
			},
			{
				"question":"Apatosaurus is also widely known by what other name?",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"Triceratops"},
				{"choice":"Brontosaurus"},
				{"choice":"It's only knows as apatosaurus"}],
				"correctAnswer":"brontosaurus"
			},
			{
				"question":"Most dinosaurs became extinct during an event that occurred 500 years ago.",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"True"},
				{"choice":"False"}],
				"correctAnswer":"false"
			},
			{
				"question":"What type of dinosaur features on the logo of the Toronto based NBA basketball team?",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"T-Rex"},
				{"choice":"Raptor"},
				{"choice":"Pterodactyl"}],
				"correctAnswer":"raptor"
			},
			{
				"question":"Dinosaur fossils have been found on every continent of Earth.",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"True"},
				{"choice":"False"}],
				"correctAnswer":"true"
			},
			{
				"question":"What dinosaur themed book was turned into a blockbuster movie in 1993?",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"Dinosaurs"},
				{"choice":"Jurassic Park"}],
				"correctAnswer":"jurassic park"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ankylosaurus featured hug plates of bone that acted as body armor.",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"True"},
				{"choice":"False"}],
				"correctAnswer":"true"
			},
			{
				"question":"Did Sauropods such as Brachiosaurus and Diplodocus move on two legs or four?",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"Two"},
				{"choice":"Four"},
				{"choice":"Sauropods swim"}],
				"correctAnswer":"four"
			},
			{
				"question":"Pentaceratops was the first dinosaur to be officially named.",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"True"},
				{"choice":"False"}],
				"correctAnswer":"false"
			},
			{
				"question":"Which came first, the Jurassic or Triassic Period?",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"Jarrasic"},
				{"choice":"Triassic"},
				{"choice":"Both aren't prehistoric periods"},
				{"choice":"Only one of those is a prehistoric period"}],
				"correctAnswer":"triassic"
			},
			{
				"question":"The US state of Colorado lists the Allosaurus as its state dinosaur.",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"True"},
				{"choice":"False"}],
				"correctAnswer":"false"
			},
			{
				"question":"What weighed more, a fully grown Spinosaurus or Deinonychus?",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"Spinosaurus"},
				{"choice":"Deinonychus"},
				{"choice":"Both aren't dinosaurs"},
				{"choice":"One isn't a dinosaur"}],
				"correctAnswer":"spinosaurus"
			},
			{
				"question":"A person who studies fossils and prehistoric life such as dinosaurs is known as a what?",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"Paleontologist"},
				{"choice":"Philanthropist"},
				{"choice":"Archeologist"}],
				"correctAnswer":"paleontologist"
			},
			{
				"question":"Birds evolved from dinosaurs.",
				"choices":[
				{"choice":"True"},
				{"choice":"False"}],
				"correctAnswer":"true"
			}
		]}